Boyars mss., 1960-2010 LMC 2953
Lilly Library
- Publishing Files
  - Turner, John F. C.
    - Housing by People - cover drafts, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Housing by People - photographs and artwork, undated (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
    - Housing by People - correspondence and files, 1976-1999 (Box 35, Folder 10-12)
    - Housing by People - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
  - Tuten, Frederic
    - Tallien: A Brief Romance - cover drafts, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Tallien: A Brief Romance - correspondence and files, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Tallien: A Brief Romance - reviews, 1988-1995 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Van Gogh's Bad Café - correspondence and files, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Van Gogh's Bad Café- page proofs (set 2), undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Van Gogh's Bad Café - reviews, 1996-1999 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - The Adventures of Mao on the Long March - correspondence and files, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 19-20)
    - The Adventures of Mao on the Long March - reviews, 1971-1997 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - The Adventures of Mao on the Long March - page proofs, undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Tintin in the World - correspondence and files, 1992-1994 (Box 35, Folder 23-24)
    - Reviews (folder 1), 1993-1999 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Reviews (folder 2), 1993-1999 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Author file, 1993-2002 (Box 36, Folder 2-3)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Verhulst, Dimitri
    - Problemski Hotel - cover proofs, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Volponi, Paolo
    - The Worldwide Machine - reviews, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Volta, Ornella
    - Satie Seen Through His Letters - reviews, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Satie Seen Through His Letters - typescript, undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Satie Seen Through His Letters - "L'Ymagier d'Erik Satie", 1979 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Satie Seen Through His Letters - correspondence and files, 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 12-13)
    - Satie Seen Through His Letters - cover drafts, undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Wachtel, Chuck
    - Joe the Engineer - reviews, 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Joe the Engineer - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Walker, Kath
    - The Dawn is at Hand - cover drafts, undated (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - The Dawn is at Hand - correspondence and files, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - The Dawn is at Hand - reviews, 1990-1993 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Walser, Martin
    - The Unicorn - correspondence and files, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Walter, Tony
    - Basic Income - cover proofs, undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Basic Income - reviews, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Weiss, Peter
    - Marat/Sade - reviews, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Marat/Sade - cover proofs, undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - The Conversation of the Three Walkers - reviews, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - The Investigation - reviews, 1988-1996 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - The Investigation - cover proofs, undated (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Notes on the Cultural Life of the Democratic Republic of Vietnam - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Welty, Eudora
    - The Collected Stories of Eudora Welty - reviews, 1981-1987 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - The Collected Stories of Eudora Welty - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Obituaries, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - West, Paul
    - Colonel Mint - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
  - White, Edgar
    - Redemption Song - reviews, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Redemption Song - correspondence and files, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Redemption Song - cover proofs, undated (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - The Rising - typescript, undated (Box 37, Folder 1-4)
    - The Rising - correspondence and files, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - The Rising - reviews, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - The Rising - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Lament for Rastafari - reviews, 1982-1993 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Lament for Rastafari - correspondence and files, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Lament for Rastafari - page proofs, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Lament for Rastafari - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Ghosts: Live from Galilee - typescript, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - That Cunard Woman - typescript, undated (Box 37, Folder 11-12)
    - The Rihla - typescript, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Wilkinson, Lettice
    - Charity Shopping & the Thrift Lifestyle - reviews, 2008-2009 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Williamson, Audrey
    - Gilbert & Sullivan - correspondence and files, 1982-1984 (Box 37, Folder 16-17)
    - Gilbert & Sullivan - artwork and photographs, undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Gilbert & Sullivan - reviews, 1982-1984 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Gilbert & Sullivan - cover proofs, undated (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Gilbert & Sullivan - cover proofs, undated (Box 72 (oversize))
  - Williamson, Judith
    - Deadline at Dawn - cover drafts, undated (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Deadline at Dawn - correspondence and files, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 22-23)
    - Deadline at Dawn - reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Decoding Advertisements - reviews, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Consuming Passions - reviews, 1986-1988 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Consuming Passions - correspondence and files, 1985-1991 (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
    - Consuming Passions - cover proofs, undated (Box 69 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Wilson, John
    - Discipline and Authority in Classroom and Courtroom - correspondence and files, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Wiseman, Thomas
    - Genius Jack - reviews, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Wistrich, Enid
    - I Don't Mind the Sex, It's the Violence - correspondence and files, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - I Don't Mind the Sex, It's the Violence - cover proofs, undated (Box 74 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Wolff, Ann
    - The Grand Master Plan - reviews, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - The Grand Master Plan - correspondence and files, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - The Grand Master Plan - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Photographs, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Wolkers, Jan
    - Turkish Delight - reviews, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Turkish Delight - correspondence and files, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Turkish Delight - cover proofs, undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Wongar, B.
    - Raki - reviews, 1983-1998 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Raki - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Worpole, Ken
    - Reading by Numbers - reviews, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Wright, Sarah E.
    - This Child's Gonna Live - correspondence and files, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Wykham, Helen
    - Ottoline Atlantica - correspondence and files, 1979-1982 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Ottoline Atlantica - cover proofs, undated (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Ottoline Atlantica - reviews, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Ottoline Atlantica - cover proofs, undated (Box 73 (oversize))
    - Ribstone Pippins - cover proofs, undated (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Ribstone Pippins - reviews, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 27)
    - Ribstone Pippins - correspondence and files, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Cavan - cover proofs, undated (Box 71 (oversize))
  - Yavin, Naftali
    - Photographs, undated (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Yevtushenko, Yevgeny
    - Almost at the End - reviews, 1987-1991 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Almost at the End - correspondence and files, 1987-1989 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Almost at the End - cover drafts, undated (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Almost at the End - cover proofs, undated (Box 70 (oversize))
    - Face Behind the Face - cover proofs, undated (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Face Behind the Face - correspondence and files, 1978-1992 (Box 38, Folder 34-35)
    - Early Poems - correspondence and files, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Early Poems - cover proofs, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Early Poems - page proofs, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Tours and readings, 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Author file, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Ying, Hong
    - The Concubine of Shanghai - reviews, 2008-2009 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - The Concubine of Shanghai - cover proofs, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - K: The Art of Love - cover proofs, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - K: The Art of Love - uncorrected proof, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - K: The Art of Love - correspondence and files, 2001-2005 (Box 39, Folder 10-14)
    - K: The Art of Love - reviews, 2002-2004 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - The Peacock Cries - correspondence and files, 2003-2004 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Zaoui, Amin
    - Banquet of Lies - reviews, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Zola, Irving
    - Photographs, undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous reviews, 1983-2008 (Box 39, Folder 20-21)
  - Miscellaneous cover proofs, undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous contracts, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Correspondence
  - A. M. Heath & Co. Ltd., 1976-1981 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - A. P. Watt, Ltd., 1962-1980 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - A. W. Bruna Uitgevers, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Ableman, Paul, 1998-2000 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Abner Stein (folders 1-4), 1975-2003 (Box 40, Folder 15-18)
  - Abner Stein (folders 5-6), 1975-2003 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Aboul-Ela, Hosam, 1991-1993 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Actac Ltd., 1976 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Acton Society, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Agathon, 1983-2007 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - L'Age d'Homme - La Cite, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Aitken & Stone, Ltd., 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Akademilitteratur, 1982-1984 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Ed. Albin Michel, 1984-1988 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1984-1990 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Allanheld, Osmun & Co. Publishers, 1976-1979 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Allied Insurance Brokers Ltd., 1982-1986 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Amboboeken, 1982-1989 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Anansi Publishers, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Anansi Canada, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Anaya & Mario Muchnik, 1981-1999 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Andrew Nurnberg Assoc. Ltd., 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Andrews, Lyman, 1967-1979 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Anglo-Hellenic Agency, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Anthony Harwood Ltd., 2001 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Anthony Sheil Assoc. Ltd., 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Aramith Uigevers bv, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Arbeiderspers, 1980-1997 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Arche Verlag, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Arnoldo Mondatori Editore, 1975-1995 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Arrow Books, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Artisjus, 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Ashmore, Basil, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Athenaeum - Netherlands, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Athenaeum - NY, 1976-1978 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Atkins, John, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Atlantic Monthly Press, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Atlantis, 1989-1992 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Avenira Stiftung, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Aventura Forlag, 1983-1984 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous publishers - A, 1976-1979 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Bar David, 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Barber, Virginia, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Barbone, Donato, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Barenreiter Verlag, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Barral Editores, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Barrows, Anita, 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Barzdo, John, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Basic Books Inc., 1976 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Beckett, Samuel, 1970-1975 (Box 41, Folder 46-47)
  - Bennett, Mark, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Beresford, Anne, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Berio, Luciano, 1984-1991 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Berlin Verlag, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Uitgeverij Bert Bakker, 1977-1985 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Bertelsmann Verlag, 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Bezige Bi, 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Bihalji-Merlin, Oto, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Birkhauser Verlag, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Blackbridge, Persimmon, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Bleys, Olivier, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Bo Ejeby Forlag, 1992-1998 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Bohm, Karl, 1990-1998 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Bokomotiv, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Bolt & Watson, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Bonniers Verlag, 1975-1980 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Book Publishers Association of Israel, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Bookblast Ltd., 1997-2002 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Born, Anne, 1991-1999 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Boston Women's Press, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 10-11)
  - Bouis, Nina, 1985-1993 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Boyars, Arthur, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Boyer, Michel, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Boyle, Godfrey, 1975-1979 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Bradshaw, John, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Brautigam, Heike, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Bray, Barbara, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Brenot, Philippe, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Brisac, Genevieve, 1993-2000 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Brokken, Jan, 2003-2005 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Ed. Buchet-Chastel, 1975-1989 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Buckman, Rosemary, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Bullock, Michael, 1986-1998 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Bureau du Livre Francais, 1989-1992 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Bureau Hongrois, 1969-1972 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Burns, Alan, 1979-1993 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Burroughs, William S., 1977 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Busch, Fred, 1978-1992 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Buss, Robin, 1993-2001 (Box 42, Folder 30-31)
  - Byk Kapauuh, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous publishers - B, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - C & J Wolfers Ltd., 1975-1978 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Calisher, Hortense, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Callaghan, Mary Rose, 1985-2000 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Ed. Calmann-Levy, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Cameron, Evan, 1992-1995 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Campbell, Thompson & Mclaughlin Ltd., 1975-1979 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Canetti, Elias, 1977-1993 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Cariad Ltd., 1979 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Carl Hanser Verlag, 1975-1979 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Carley, Lionel, 1992-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
  - Carmen Balcells, 1986-2002 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Casterman Publishers, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Catedra, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Cecilio Cardenoso, 1975-1979 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Editions du CERF, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Chandler Crawford Agency Inc., 1999-2001 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Charles River Press Inc., 1976 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Charters, Sam, 1979-1981 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Ed. du Chene, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Christian Bourgeois Editeur, 1976-1980 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Civilizacao Editoria Portugal, 2004 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Clark, Lester, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Clausen, Claus, 1983-1997 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Coe, Richard, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Coffee House Press, 1999-2000 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Cohen, Nicholas, 1982-1987 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Coleman, Maxwell, 1990-1994 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Collins, 1976-1978 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Collins, Clive, 1988-1991 (Box 43, Folder 21-23)
  - Columna, 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Creeley, Robert, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Uitgeverij Contact, 1994-1997 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Crescendo Press, 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Crosland, Margaret, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Croton Press, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Curbstone Press, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Curtis Brown Ltd., 1972-1980 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Custen, George F., 1998 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Cynthia Parzych Publishing, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Czerniawski, Adam, 1966-1995 (Box 43, Folder 34-36)
  - Miscellaneous publishers - C, 1972-1977 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Dalton, David, 1999-2000 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  - Darke, Helmut S., 1969-1977 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Darrill, Keith, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Dauber, Heinrich, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  - David Grossman, 1993-2004 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  - David Higham Assoc. Ltd., 1976-1977 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  - Davie, Elspeth, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  - de Obaldia, Rene, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  - Ed. La Decouverte, 1990-1998 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  - Dedomenico, Peter F., 1996 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Dennis, Franklin, 1985-1990 (Box 44, Folder 1-2)
  - Denoel, 1990-1996 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Di Giovanni, Norman, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Dial Press, 1970-1979 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Diamond, Stephen, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Dickson, Paul, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Diogenes Verlag, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - The Dolmen Press, 1976-1979 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Domena, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Dorfman, Ariel, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Dormandy, Thomas, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Douglas Rae Management Ltd., 1975 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Dumont, Louis, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Duras, Marguerite, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - ECON Verlagsgruppe, 1981-1993 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Ed Victor Ltd., 1980 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Edite Kroll, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Edwards, Gwynne, 1982-2002 (Box 44, Folder 19-20)
  - Edwards, Page, 1979-1998 (Box 44, Folder 21-25)
  - Edwards, Page (posthumous), 1999 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Elaine Greene Ltd., 1966-1979 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Ellen Levine, 1999-2000 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - "Embassies", 2003 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Emery, Jack, 1976-1980 (Box 44, Folder 30-31)
  - Eric Yang Agency, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - "European Reps", 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Evans, Pamela, 1975-1980 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Eyre, Peter, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous - E, 1975-1978 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Facey, Philip A., 1982-1984 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Fayyad, Soleiman, 1992-1993 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Feinstein, Elaine, 1997-2001 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Fen, Elisavelia, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Figgis, Pamela, 1980-1999 (Box 45, Folder 9-10)
  - Ed. Filipacchi, 1994-1997 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Fineberg, Michael, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Finnegan, Seamus, 1986-1999 (Box 45, Folder 13-14)
  - Fischer Taschenbuch Verlag, 1995-1997 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Fitzlyon, Kyril, 1975-1980 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Fletcher, John, 1975-1986 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Fondo de Cultura Economica, 1989-2000 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Forum (Sweden), 1987-2000 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Foster, Joseph, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Foundation for the Promotion of the Translation of Dutch Literary Works, 1981-1992 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Franco Muzzio & C., 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Franklin, Charlotte, 1993-2000 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Franklin, Colin, 1980-1983 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Franklin, Simon, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Fraser & Dunlop Scripts Ltd., 1976-1979 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Frederique Porretta, undated (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - French Institute, 1996-2003 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - French Publishers' Agency, 1996-1997 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Friedman, Melvin, 1972-1974 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Fyfe, Mark, 1996-2004 (Box 45, Folder 31-32)
  - Miscellaneous - F, 1973-1979 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Gadol, Peter, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Gangemi, Kenneth, 1977-1980 (Box 46, Folder 2-3)
  - Gardner, Richard, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Gebler, Carlo, 1997-2002 (Box 46, Folder 5-6)
  - Geddes, Tom, 1999-2002 (Box 46, Folder 7-9)
  - Gelles, Walter, 1976-1984 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - George Braziller Inc., 1976-1980 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - George Philip & Son Ltd., 1978-1980 (Box 46, Folder 12-13)
  - George Philip Services Ltd., 1986-1987 (Box 46, Folder 14-15)
  - Georges Borchardt, Inc., 1976-2006 (Box 46, Folder 16-17)
  - Gombrowicz, Witold, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Goodman, David, 1979-1981 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Goodman, Derrick & Co., 1972-1976 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Goodwin, Clive, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Gora, Tom, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Goulet, Robert, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Gredos, 1980-1997 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Green, Julien, 1990-2006 (Box 46, Folder 25-27)
  - Greenslade, Roy, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Grey, Antony, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Griffith-Jones, Krystyna, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Griffiths, Gareth, 1977-1980 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Gyldenhal, 1975-2001 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - H. Aschehoug & Co., 1997 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - H. Blume, 1975-1999 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Hachette, 1979-1988 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Hamburger, Michael, 1970-2003 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Hamilton, Alastair, 1975-1977 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Hamlyn Paperbacks, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Hamrell, Sven, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Hanna-Kirsti Koch, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Hans Reitzels Forlag, 1975-1980 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc., 1976-1980 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Hauch, Christine, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Havas Poche, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Hawkins-Creeley, Bobbie, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Heath, Roy, 1996-1998 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Hehn, Katharina, 1978-1980 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Heilbroner, Robert L., 1975-1978 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Heinrich Hanau Pub. Ltd., 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Helena Strassova, 1982-1984 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Hemming, James, 1978-1980 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Henry, Faith, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Heppenstall, Rayner, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Het Wereldvenster, 1981-1983 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Hobin, Tina, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Hoch, Paul, 1976-1980 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Hogan, Des, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Hollings, Ken, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Hollington, Michael, 1978-1984 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Holt, John, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Hood, Stuart, 1970-1977 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Hope Leresche & Sayle, 1975-1978 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Hopkins, Bill, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Horovitz, Michael, 1978-1988 (Box 47, Folder 34-35)
  - Howell, Anthony, 1975-2000 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Hughes Massie Ltd., 1977-1980 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Hummelinck, M. G. W., 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Hunter Rose Co., 1979 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Hyde, George, 1972-1979 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Imprint, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Indiana University Press, 1981-1988 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Insel Verlag, 1987-1997 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Instituto Cervantes, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - International Creative Management Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - International Editors Co., 1979 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - Interrights, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - Iowa State University Press, 1989-1992 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - Iperborea, 1987-2001 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - IPS Copyright Agency, 1992-1995 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - "Irish representation", 1980-1981 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Isis, 1992-1993 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Ives, Charles, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Iwanami Shoten, 1980-1996 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - J. W. Cappelens Forlag, 1997-2003 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Jackson, Brian, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Jaico, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Japan Uni Agency, Inc., 1975-1980 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Jarrett, Virginia, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Jenkins, Hugh, 1977-1979 (Box 48, Folder 10-11)
  - Joans, Ted, 1976-1978 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - John Farquharson Ltd., 1975-1987 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - John Johnson Ltd., 1976-1981 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Jones & Partners, 1979-1982 (Box 48, Folder 15-17)
  - Jorge Zahar, 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Justin, Charles & Co., 2002 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Kael, Pauline, 1970-1980 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Karsov, Nina, 1979-1982 (Box 48, Folder 21)